babynamenetwork.com 2012-04-15

# Baby Names, Baby Boy Names, Baby Girl Names, Baby Name Meanings

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**Your Consent and Rights**

By using our website you consent to the collection and use of this information by The Baby Name Network. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted to this page so that you are kept informed of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

  * **Registration Information**  
You will provide us information about yourself and your practices when you register to be a member of Baby Name Network. 
  * **Email Information**  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

**Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them. 

**Approved Member Web Sites**

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on message boards, or in chat areas, for example, originating from our members area, this information can be potentially viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge or even an approved Web site's knowledge. This may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Baby Name Network and this privacy policy, and it is strongly advised you use extreme care and understand applicable privacy policies when visiting third party links originating from our site. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to Baby Name Network. For that reason, we never knowingly collect or maintain personal information at our Web site from those that are under the age of 13. In fact, no part of this Web site is structured or designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number, email and your practices for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

**The Controls You Have On Information You Share**

If you do not want us to share contact, postal, e-mail address and demographic information with third party marketers, email [help@babynamenetwork.com](mailto:help@babynamenetwork.com). You can opt out of third party and advertising networks by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

In addition, you may request to be removed from our membership list at any time by emailing [help@babynamenetwork.com](mailto:help@babynamenetwork.com). 

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you visit our Web site, the site uses its cookies to customize the members area content for you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at [help@babynamenetwork.com](mailto:help@babynamenetwork.com).

**Third Party Services**

From time-to-time, we may partner with other parties to provide specific services. It may be necessary to share names, or other contact information with a third party(ies) to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Baby Name Network, are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website. When you are on the Baby Name Network site or are accessing a Baby Name Network promotion through an advertising vehicle, and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Baby Name Network. Promotions, surveys and other sweepstakes offerings may be sponsored, or co-sponsored, by another company. Some or all of the data collected during such a program may be shared with the marketing partner. Your participation is always voluntary. 

**Tell Us What You Think**

Baby Name Network welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please e-mail us at [help@babynamenetwork.com](mailto:help@babynamenetwork.com). 

Custom Search 

---
